

Bali, Indonesia ↑
+6282210462723 ↓
sadam9@outlook.co.id ☑
sadam21x in
https://sadam.dev ⊕

I'm Sadam, a Software Engineer from Bali, Indonesia. I specialize in web development with 2+ years of experience in handling small to medium-scale web application projects. I am a framework-agnostic person and can easily adapt to any technology to achieve high-quality results. I have the ability to work in both individual and collaborative working environments.

Skills

- Front-end Web Development (CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React)
- Back-end Web Development (Node.js, Go, PHP, Laravel, REST API)
- Database (MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase, MongoDB)
- Other Tools (Git, Docker, Cloud VPS)

Experience

May 2022 - December 2022 | Contract | Surabaya, Indonesia (Remote)

Web Developer | PT Wiraharja Graha Software

- Took part in the geniebook.com homepage revamp project.
- Develop REST API for a pharmacy management application.
- Most used tech-stack: CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Go and MySQL.

Apr 2022 - November 2022 | Internship | Singapore (Remote)

Front-end Software Engineer | Jojobug Tech Pte. Ltd.

- Developed some of the main features of Jojobug Blog Web App, such as post editor, article page, and several APIs.
- Develop several web templates based on Figma designs created by the UI team.
- Took part in Jojobug Landing Page development.
- Most used tech-stack: TypeScript, Node.js, React, Next.js, Tailwind, and Firebase.

Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 | Internship | Surabaya, Indonesia (Remote)

Web Developer | DPKKA Universitas Airlangga

- Designed, developed, and integrated new features for the DPKKA Website, such as a live-chat helpdesk, newsletter, and career counseling app.
- Maintained the Universitas Airlangga Alumni Website's Server.
- Assist with IT-related work at several events, such as Airlangga Online Career Fair (AOCF).
- Most used tech-stack: Vue, PHP, Laravel Framework, and MySQL.

Education

Aug 2018 - Jan 2022 | Surabaya, East Java Indonesia

Associate's Degree, Information System | Universitas Airlangga

- Graduated with Cumlaude predicate (GPA 3.52/4.00).
- Served as Communication and Informatics Staff of the Information System Student Association during the 2019-2021 period.
- Served as Communication and Informatics Staff of the Student Executive Board of the Faculty of Vocational Studies during the 2019-2020 period.

Certification

Sep 2021 - Sep 2024

Junior Web Developer | Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP)

View/Download certificate: https://sadam.dev/download/BNSP Junior Web Developer Sadam.pdf

Project

2022 | API

LayanObat Mitra

LayanObat Mitra is an application programming interface (API) for pharmacy management applications. Some the key features include stock management, orders, sales, and reporting.

Tech: Go, Gin Framework, and MySQL.

2022 | Web Application | https://tracerstudy.unair.ac.id

Airlangga Tracer Study System (ATSS)

ATSS is a web-based application to collect data about alumni careers after college through online surveys. Some of the key features include survey creation, email blaster, and reporting.

Tech: Vue, PHP, Laravel Framework, and PostgreSQL.

2021 | Web Application | https://dpkka.unair.ac.id/ext/counseling

Career Counseling App (CCA) DPKKA Universitas Airlangga

CCA is a web-based chat application to help students and alumni find their career paths by chatting with counselors provided by the university. Some of the key features include counseling scheduling, invitation email, and chat room with data encryption.

Tech: Vue, PHP, Laravel Framework, and MySQL.

2020 | Web Application | https://esertif.vokasiunair.com

E-Sertifikat Fakultas Vokasi Universitas Airlangga

A web-based application used by the Faculty to create and distribute e-certificates to students. Certificates such as certificates for seminars, webinars, organizations, etc.

Tech: PHP, Laravel Framework, and MySQL.